games-guides.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Guides for Trophies, Achievements, Collectibles and more

We, the company Jean-Pierre Binsack, take the protection of your personal data very seriously and adhere strictly to the rules of data protection laws.

Personal data is gathered on this website solely to the extent that is technically necessary. In no event will the gathered data be sold or otherwise transferred to third parties. We use the data you provide us to carry out and complete your order.

The following policy gives you an overview of how we ensure this data protection and which kinds of data are gathered for what purpose.

## Data Processing on the Website of Games Guides

In its server log files, Jean-Pierre Binsack collects and automatically saves information that your browser sends to us. This information consists of:

  * Browser type and version
  * Operating system
  * Referrer URL (previously visited page)
  * Hostname of the accessing computer (IP address)
  * Time of the server reques.

Jean-Pierre Binsack cannot attribute the above data to specific individuals. This data will not be combined with other data sources and, furthermore, the data will be deleted after statistical analysis.

## Information about Cookies

Our website makes use of cookies in several places. These serve to make our website and services more user-friendly, effective and safe. Cookies are small text files that are saved by your browser and stored on your computer. Most of the cookies we use are so-called “session cookies”.

These cookies are deleted automatically after your visit. Cookies on your computer do not harm your computer and do not contain viruses.

### What is a Cookie?

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer when you visit a website. This text file stores information that can be read by the website if you visit it again later. Some cookies are necessary to ensure that the website functions correctly. Other cookies are beneficial for visitors: they store the username and other information – for example, the language settings – in a secure fashion. The purpose of cookies is to ensure that you do not have to enter the same information each time you visit the website.

### Why does Game Guides use cookies?

Game Guides uses cookies to fulfil your needs as a customer in providing you an optimally tailored web-browsing and shopping experience. In using cookies, Game Guides can make sure that you are not presented with identical information each time you visit the website. Cookies can also eliminate the need for you to enter the same information twice. Cookies may also be used to optimize the performance of a website. They facilitate, for example, the logout process and help you to find specific products more quickly.

In order to protect your personal information, and to prevent loss of information or unlawful behavior, Game Guides employs appropriate organisational and technical measures.

### How can I disable cookies?

You can easily adjust your browser settings to disable all cookies. Please note: If you disable cookies, then your username and password will no longer be stored on the website and all other data that you have stored for this site, such as your customized car, will be lost.

#### Firefox:

  1. Open Firefox.
  2. Press the “alt” key on your keyboard.
  3. In the toolbar at the top of your browser, select “Tools” and then “Options”
  4. Select the “privacy” tab.
  5. Go to “Settings History” and then “Use custom settings”.
  6. Uncheck “Accept cookies from sites” and save your preferences

#### Internet Explorer:

  1. Open Internet Explorer.
  2. Click on “Tools” and then “Internet Options”.
  3. Select the “Privacy” tab.
  4. Select the “Advanced” button.
  5. Under “First-party Cookies” and “Third-party Cookies”, choose “Block” to automatically block all cookies
  6. Click “Ok”.

#### Google Chrome:

  1. Open Google Chrome.
  2. Click on “Tools”.
  3. Select “Settings” and then “Advanced Settings”.
  4. Select “Content Settings” in the “Privacy” section.
  5. You can deselect cookies and save your preferences in the “Cookies” section

#### Safari:

  1. Open Safari.
  2. Select the “Preferences” option in the tool bar and then select the “Privacy” panel in the following dialogue box.
  3. Under “Cookies and website data” you can specify if and when Safari should accept cookies from websites. For more information click on the Help (?) button.
  4. For more information on the cookies that are stored on your computer, click on “Details”.

## Leaving Comments & Requesting Removal of your Comments

When leaving a comment below a post your IP (internet protocol) address will be stored on our server, but we have activated an IP anonymization. Furthermore, you must enter an email address to leave a comment. A log file with the email address you entered will be stored on our server and can only be seen by the admin and moderation team. This is done strictly for spam prevention purposes and to process comment removals as per your request (because this site doesn’t offer user signups it’s the only way for us to verify you are the comment author). If you would like one of your comments removed please contact [info@games-guides.com](mailto:info@games-guides.com) with the email address you used for submitting your comment. We will never give your email address to third parties and you will never receive emails about replies to your comments.

## Right to Information

You always have the right to receive information concerning your stored personal data, its origin and recipient as well as the purpose of its storage. The Data Protection Officer of the company Jean-Pierre Binsack provides information about stored data:

**Jean-Pierre Binsack**  
Data Protection Officer  
E-Mail: [info@games-guides.com](mailto:info@games-guides.com)

In accordance with the Federal Data Protection Act, you have a right to information free of charge about your stored data and a right to correct, block or erase this data

For questions regarding the collection, processing and use of your personal data, as well as the disclosure, correction, blocking or deletion of data please contact:

**Jean-Pierre Binsack**  
Data Protection Officer  
E-Mail: [info@games-guides.com](mailto:info@games-guides.com)

## Google AdSense

This website uses Google AdSense, a service for integrating advertisements of Google Inc. (“Google”). Provider is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.

Google AdSense uses so-called “cookies”, text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website. Google AdSense also uses so-called web beacons (invisible graphics). These web beacons can be used to evaluate information such as visitor traffic on these pages.

The information generated by cookies and web beacons on the use of this website (including your IP address) and delivery of advertising formats are transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the USA. This information may be shared by Google with Google affiliates. However, Google will not merge your IP address with other data you have stored.

The storage of AdSense cookies is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior in order to optimize both its website and its advertising.

You can prevent the installation of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly; however, please note that in this case you may not be able to use all features of this website to the fullest extent. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

## Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, which are text files that are stored on your computer and enable analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie concerning your use of this website is usually transferred to a Google server in the United States and stored there. If IP anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will, however, be truncated by Google beforehand within the area of the member states of the European Union or other states party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the United States and truncated there.

Google will use this information on behalf of this website’s owner to evaluate your use of the website, compile reports about website activities, and provide the website’s operator with further services related to website and Internet usage. The IP address sent by your browser as required by Google Analytics is not merged with other data by Google.

You can prevent storage of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser software. If you do this, however, please note that you might not be able to use all the functions of the website. You can also prevent the data generated by the cookie, and the data related to your usage of this website (including your IP address), from being sent to and processed by Google by downloading and installing a browser plug-in available through the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB>

Click here to disable the Google Analytics tracking directly.

For more information, see <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB> and <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en> (general information on Google Analytics and data protection). Please note that this website uses Google Analytics with the extension “gat._anonymizeIp();” in order to anonymise the IP addresses by deleting the last octet of the IP address.

## Use of Facebook Social Plugins

This website uses so-called social plugins (“plugins”) from the social network Facebook, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). You can find an overview of Facebook plugins and their appearance at: <https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins>.

If you access a page from our website that contains such a plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook’s servers. Facebook sends the contents of the plugin directly to your browser and embeds them into the web page. This process enables Facebook to receive the information that your browser has accessed the corresponding page of our website, even if you do not have a Facebook account or are not logged in with Facebook at the time. This information (including your IP address) is sent by your browser directly to a Facebook server in the United States and is stored there.

If you are logged into Facebook, Facebook can then attribute the visit to our website directly to your Facebook account. If you interact with the plugins – for example, if you click on the ‘Like‘ button or submit a comment – the corresponding information will be sent directly to a Facebook server and stored there. The information will also be published on Facebook and shown to your Facebook friends.

Facebook may use this information for the purposes of advertising, market research and the personalized design of Facebook pages. To this end, Facebook creates usage, interest and relationship profiles, e.g. to analyse your use of our website with regard to the advertisements that Facebook displays to you, to inform other Facebook users about your activities on our web site, and to provide further services associated with the use of Facebook.

If you do not want Facebook to collect data about you via our website and to attribute this to your Facebook account, you should log out of your Facebook account before visiting our website.

The purpose and scope of data collection and ongoing processing and use of data by Facebook, as well as your rights and the setting options for protecting your privacy can be found in the Facebook privacy policy here: <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

## Conversion Measurement with Facebook’s Conversion Tracking Pixel

With your consent, we will use the conversion tracking pixel of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, United States (hereinafter: “Facebook”) on our website. With the aid of this tool, we can track the actions of users after they have seen or clicked on a Facebook advertisement. This allows us to record the effectiveness of Facebook advertisements for statistical and market research purposes. The data collected in this manner is anonymous for us, which means we do not see the personal data of individual users. However, this data is saved and processed by Facebook. We are informing you of this process based on the current information available to us. Facebook can link this data with your Facebook account and use it for its own advertising purposes in accordance with Facebook’s data policy at <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>. This data can enable Facebook and its partners to insert advertisements on Facebook and outside Facebook. Furthermore, a cookie can be saved on your computer to this end.

## Further Information

Your trust is important to us. We are, therefore, always happy to discuss this policy with you and answer any questions you may have concerning the processing of your personal data. If you have any questions that this Privacy Policy was unable to answer, or if you wish to receive more information, please consult our data protection officer at any time:

**Jean-Pierre Binsack**  
Data Protection Officer  
E-Mail: [info@games-guides.com](mailto:info@games-guides.com)

## Liability Limitation

Great care has been taken in creating the contents of our website. However Jean-Pierre Binsack cannot guarantee that the contents are accurate, complete and up to date. The usage of the website contents takes place at the user’s risk. All content bearing the name of the author reflects the opinion of the author only and does not necessarily represent the opinion of the Games Guides GmbH & Co. KG. Simply using the website of Games Guides GmbH & Co. KG does not establish a contractual relationship between the user and the provider.

### External Links

Our website contains links to other websites (“external links”). These websites are the responsibility of the respective operators. Jean-Pierre Binsack has no influence whatsoever on the design and content of linked sites. The placing of external links on the website of Jean-Pierre Binsack does not mean that Jean-Pierre Binsack takes possession of the content behind the reference or link.

### Copyright and Intellectual Property Law

Individual content published on our website is subject to German copyright and intellectual property law. Any use not permitted under German copyright and intellectual property law requires the prior written consent of Jean-Pierre Binsack or the relevant copyright holder. This applies in particular to copying, editing, translation, search engine optimization (on-page as well as off-page optimization), storage, processing or reproduction of content in databases or other electronic media and systems. Contents and rights of third parties are marked as such. The unauthorized reproduction or distribution of content or complete pages is prohibited and punishable by law. Only the production of copies, and downloads for personal, private and not for commercial use, are permitted.

Presentation of this website in external frames is only permitted with written permission.
